American Scholar Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part I: Accession No. 13,595, General Editorial File, 1932-1957 (Box I:30)
  - 1954-1955
    - Editorial
      - Portraits, Alvin Johnson, winter 1954-1955
      - "The Reader Replies"
        - Autumn 1954
        - Winter 1954-1955
        - Spring 1955
        - Summer 1955
      - "The Revolving Bookstand"
        - Committee
        - Publishers
          - Commercial
          - University presses
        - Reviewers
          - Autumn 1954
          - Winter 1954-1955
          - Spring 1955
          - Summer 1955
          - Miscellaneous, 1954-1955
      - "Scholar's Scratch Pad"
        - Winter 1954-1955
        - Spring 1955
    - Printing and production, William Byrd Press (Box I:25)
    - Promotion and publicity
      - Correspondence
      - Press releases
      - Special mailings
        - Miscellaneous, 1954-1955
        - Spring 1955
  - 1955-1956
    - Advertising
      - James, William and Eleanor
      - Miscellaneous
    - Circulation, bookstores and newsstands
    - Editorial
      - Board
        - Meetings
        - Members
      - General
      - Haydn, Hiram (Box I:26)
        - Personal file
        - Phi Beta Kappa
        - American Scholar
      - Manuscripts received
      - Personnel
      - "The Reader Replies"
        - Autumn 1955
        - Spring 1956
        - Summer 1956
        - Miscellaneous, 1955-1956
      - "The Revolving Bookstand"
        - Committee
        - Publishers
          - Commercial
          - University presses
        - Reviewers
          - Autumn 1955
          - Winter 1955-1956 (Box I:27)
          - Spring 1956
          - Summer 1956
          - Miscellaneous, 1955-1956
      - "Scholar's Scratch Pad," summer 1956
    - Printing and production, William Byrd Press
    - Promotion and publicity
      - Correspondence
      - Special mailings, autumn 1955
  - 1956-1957 (Box I:28)
    - Advertising
      - James, William and Eleanor
      - Miscellaneous
    - Circulation
      - Analysis, May 1957
      - Bookstores and newsstands
    - Editorial
      - Board members
      - Forums (controversy), spring 1957
      - General
      - Haydn, Hiram
        - Personal
        - Phi Beta Kappa
        - American Scholar
      - Manuscripts received
      - Personnel
      - Portraits, summer 1957
      - "The Reader Replies" (Box I:29)
        - Autumn 1956
        - Winter 1956-1957
        - Spring 1957
        - Summer 1957
        - Miscellaneous, 1956-1957
      - "The Revolving Bookstand"
        - Committee
        - Publishers
          - Commercial
          - University presses
        - Reviewers
          - Autumn 1956
          - Winter 1956-1957
          - Spring 1957
          - Summer 1957 (Box I:30)
          - Miscellaneous, 1956-1957
        - "Scholar's Scratch Pad," summer 1957
    - Printing and production, William Byrd Press
    - Promotion and publicity
      - Correspondence
      - Miscellaneous
      - Press releases
- Part I: Accession No. 13,595, Miscellaneous, 1957-1960 (Box I:31)
  Undated letters, clippings, and reprints from the American Scholar that postdates other files in this accession. Organized by type of material.
  - Unfiled material, 1957-1960 (Box I:31)
  - Undated letters
  - Clippings and reprints from American Scholar
- Part I: Accession No. 13,595, Author File, circa 1930s-1957 (Box I:32-67)
  Correspondence with authors of articles and poems. Includes correspondence with authors whose manuscripts were rejected and those who turned down invitations to submit articles.
  Arranged chronologically by fiscal year (Aug-July) and therein alphabetically by author. An appendix of select correspondents in the file is available in the Manuscript Division Reading Room.
  - Pre-1946 (Box I:32)
    - A-Cl, (4 folders)
    - Coh-Gor, (13 folders) (Box I:33)
    - Gou-Kand, (11 folders) (Box I:34)
    - Kant-Mc, (12 folders) (Box I:35)
    - Me-Rz, (11 folders) (Box I:36)
    - Sa-We, (13 folders) (Box I:37)
    - Wh-Z, (5 folders) (Box I:38)
  - 1946-1947
    - A-Ce, (8 folders)
    - Ch-Gl, (12 folders) (Box I:39)
    - Go-Kz, (12 folders) (Box I:40)
    - La-Ri, (12 folders) (Box I:41)
    - Ro-Wi, (13 folders) (Box I:42)
    - Wo-Z, (2 folders) (Box I:43)
  - 1947-1948
    - A-Dz, (11 folders)
    - E-Lz, (15 folders) (Box I:44)
    - Ma-U, (15 folders) (Box I:45)
    - V-Z, (5 folders) (Box I:46)
  - 1948-1949
    - A-Fl, (11 folders)
    - Fo-P, (17 folders) (Box I:47)
    - Ra-Z, (10 folders) (Box I:48)
  - 1949-1950
    - A-B, (4 folders)
    - Ca-I, (14 folders) (Box I:49)
    - J-R, (13 folders) (Box I:50)
  - 1949-1950 (Box I:51)
    - Sa-Z, (7 folders)
  - 1950-1951
    - A-E, (7 folders)
    - F-Q, (17 folders) (Box I:52)
    - R-Z, (9 folders) (Box I:53)
  - 1951-1952
    - A-Bo, (9 folders)
    - Br-He, (12 folders) (Box I:54)
    - Hi-Rz, (14 folders) (Box I:55)
    - Sa-Z, (9 folders) (Box I:56)
  - 1952-1953
    - A-Ca, (5 folders)
    - Ch-K, (13 folders) (Box I:57)
    - La-Sta, (13 folders) (Box I:58)
    - Ste-Z, (7 folders) (Box I:59)
  - 1953-1954
    - A-E, (7 folders)
    - F-M, (14 folders) (Box I:60)
    - N-Z, (13 folders) (Box I:61)
  - 1954-1955
    - A
    - B-Hol, (12 folders) (Box I:62)
    - Hoo-Se, (15 folders) (Box I:63)
    - Sh-Z, (7 folders) (Box I:64)
  - 1955-1956
    - A-F, (7 folders)
    - G-V, (14 folders) (Box I:65)
    - W (Box I:66)
  - 1956-1957
    - A-L, (15 folders)
    - M-Z, (11 folders) (Box I:67)
  - 1952-1955, editorial comment sheets
- Part I: Accession No. 15,221, General Editorial File, 1957-1960 (Box I:68-74)
  Arranged chronologically by fiscal year (Aug-July) and therein by subject.
  - 1957-1958 (Box I:68)
    - Advertising representative, Eleanor James
    - Editorial
      - Board
        - Elections
        - Meetings
        - Members, 1955-1958
      - "The Revolving Bookstand"
        - Committee
        - Publishers
          - Commercial
          - University presses
        - Reviewers
          - Autumn 1957
          - Winter 1957-1958
          - Spring 1958 (Box I:69)
          - Summer 1958
          - Miscellaneous, 1957-1958
      - Copyright transfers
      - Editorials
      - Forums
      - General
      - Haydn, Hiram
        - Personal file
        - Phi Beta Kappa
        - American Scholar
      - Index
      - Manuscripts received, Aug. 1957-July 1958
      - Miscellaneous
      - Personnel (Box I:70)
      - "The Reader Replies"
        - Autumn 1957
        - Winter 1957-1958
        - Spring 1958
        - Summer 1958
        - Miscellaneous, 1957-1958
      - Reprint permissions
  - 1958-1959
    - Advertising
      - Representative, Eleanor James
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Editorial
      - Board members
      - "The Revolving Bookstand"
        - Committee
        - Publishers
          - Commercial
          - University presses
        - Reviewers
          - Autumn 1958
          - Winter 1958-1959
          - Spring 1959 (Box I:71)
          - Summer 1959
          - Miscellaneous, 1958-1959
      - Copyright transfers
      - Forums, (2 folders)
      - General
        - Autumn 1958
        - Miscellaneous
      - Haydn, Hiram
        - Personal file
        - Phi Beta Kappa
        - American Scholar
      - Manuscripts received, Aug. 1958-July 1959
      - Miscellaneous
      - Personnel
      - Poetry issue, summer 1959 (Box I:72)
        - Contest correspondence, finalists, judges, promotion, winners, contestants, (2 folders)
        - General
      - "The Reader Replies"
        - Winter 1958-1959
        - Spring 1959
        - Summer 1959
        - Miscellaneous, 1958-1959
      - Reprint permissions
      - "Scholar's Scratch Pad," winter 1958-1959
    - Printing and production, William Byrd Press, Aug. 1958-July 1959
  - 1959-1960 (Box I:73)
    - Advertising
      - Representative, Eleanor James
      - Miscellaneous
    - Editorial
      - Board members
      - "The Revolving Bookstand"
        - Publishers
          - Commercial
          - University presses
        - Reviewers
          - Autumn 1959
          - Winter 1959-1960
          - Spring 1960
          - Summer 1960
          - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960
        - Copyright transfers
      - Editorials (Box I:74)
      - Forums
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Haydn, Hiram
        - Personal file
        - Phi Beta Kappa
        - American Scholar
      - Personnel
      - "The Reader Replies"
        - Autumn 1959
        - Winter 1959-1960
        - Spring 1960
        - Summer 1960
      - Reprint permissions
    - Printing and production, William Byrd Press
      - General
      - Bills and estimates
      - Miscellaneous
- Part I: Accession No. 15,221, Author File, 1957-1960 (Box I:75-79)
  Arranged chronologically by fiscal year (Aug-July) and therein alphabetically by author.
  - 1957-1958 (Box I:75)
    - A-O, (16 folders)
    - P-Z, (11 folders) (Box I:76)
  - 1958-1959
    - A-E, (5 folders)
  - 1958-1959 (Box I:77)
    - F-R, (14 folders)
    - S-Z, (8 folders) (Box I:78)
  - 1959-1960
    - A-H, (8 folders)
    - I-Z, (19 folders) (Box I:79)
- Part I: Accession No. 15,221, Miscellaneous, 1926-1965 (Box I:80-84)
  Correspondence, memoranda, and other items that relate to earlier or later accessions.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1926-1933 (Box I:80)
  - circa 1931-1933, promotion and publicity
  - circa 1932-1938, (3 folders)
  - circa 1935-1938
    - Erskine, John
    - General, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box I:81)
    - Permissions
  - 1937, expiration letters
  - 1938
    - Graham, William C.
    - General
  - 1930s, reprints for authors
  - circa 1940-1944
  - circa 1940-1945, (3 folders) (Box I:82)
  - 1942, sample copies sent out
  - 1942-1943
    - Copies to go on author's request
    - Wilson H. Lee Co.
  - circa 1943-1944, Wendell L. Willkie
  - 1943, advertisements for summer issue
  - 1944, special circulation projects
  - 1946-1947, "Brown" book, log of articles submitted
  - 1947-1950, "Brown" book, log of articles submitted, (3 folders) (Box I:83)
  - 1952-1953, inactive projects
  - 1952-1954, M
  - 1952-1957
  - 1953-1955, incomplete
  - 1954
    - Prospective manuscripts
    - Editorial comments
  - circa 1954-1955, book correspondence
  - 1956
  - circa 1953-1961 (Box I:84)
  - circa 1955-1965
    - "Black" notebook, log of articles submitted
    - Haydn, Hiram
  - 1960-1961
    - Haydn, Hiram
    - General, (3 folders)
  - 1961-1962
    - General
    - Haydn, Hiram, and Mary Moore Molony
    - William Byrd Press
  - Undated, editorial production
- Part I: Accession No. 16,509, Author File, 1960-1970 (Box I:85-115)
  - 1960-1961 (Box I:85)
    - A-F, (6 folders)
    - G-Q, (11 folders) (Box I:86)
    - R-Z, (9 folders) (Box I:87)
  - 1961-1962
    - A-B, (2 folders)
    - C-I, (7 folders) (Box I:88)
  - 1961-1962 (Box I:89)
    - J-R, (9 folders)
    - S-Z, (8 folders) (Box I:90)
  - 1962-1963
    - A-B, (2 folders)
    - C-H, (6 folders) (Box I:91)
    - I-R, (10 folders) (Box I:92)
    - S-Z, (8 folders) (Box I:93)
    - General
  - 1963-1964
    - A-B, (2 folders)
    - C-I, (7 folders) (Box I:94)
    - J-Q, (8 folders) (Box I:95)
    - R-Z, (7 folders) (Box I:96)
  - 1964-1965 (Box I:97)
    - A-E, (5 folders)
    - F-Mc, (8 folders) (Box I:98)
    - M-V, (10 folders) (Box I:99)
    - W-Z, (2 folders) (Box I:100)
  - 1965-1966
    - A-D, (4 folders)
    - E-L, (8 folders) (Box I:101)
    - M-S, (8 folders) (Box I:102)
    - T-Z, (5 folders) (Box I:103)
  - 1966-1967
    - A-C, (3 folders)
    - D-L, (9 folders) (Box I:104)
    - M-S, (8 folders) (Box I:105)
    - T-Z, (5 folders) (Box I:106)
  - 1967-1968
    - A-E, (5 folders)
    - F-Mc, (8 folders) (Box I:107)
    - M-S, (7 folders) (Box I:108)
    - T-Z, (5 folders) (Box I:109)
  - 1968-1969
    - A-E, (5 folders)
  - 1968-1969 (Box I:110)
    - F-M, (9 folders)
    - N-Z, (11 folders) (Box I:111)
  - 1969-1970
    - A
    - B-G, (6 folders) (Box I:112)
    - H-Mc, (6 folders) (Box I:113)
    - M-U, (9 folders) (Box I:114)
    - V-W, (2 folders) (Box I:115)
- Part I: Accession No. 16,509, General Editorial File, 1951-1970 (Box I:115-137)
  - Articles solicited, autumn 1964 special issue (Box I:115)
  - Board
    - Elections, 1964-1967, (4 folders)
    - Members
      - Expired terms
        - 1965-1968, (4 folders)
        - 1969-1971, (2 folders) (Box I:116)
      - Members, 1952-1960, (4 folders)
  - Books, 1960-1961
  - Book reviews, university presses, spring 1964
  - "The Revolving Bookstand"
    - Autumn 1968
    - Winter 1968-1969 (Box I:117)
    - Spring 1969
    - Autumn 1969
    - Winter 1969-1970
    - Spring 1970
    - Summer 1970
    - Committee
    - Publishers
      - Commercial, 1960-1969, (9 folders)
      - University presses, 1960-1970, (11 folders)
    - Neglected books, spring 1970 (Box I:118)
    - Reviewers
      - Autumn 1960
      - Winter 1960
      - Spring 1961
      - Summer 1961
      - Autumn 1961 (Box I:119)
      - Winter 1961
      - Spring 1962
      - Summer 1962
      - Autumn 1962
      - Winter 1962
      - Spring 1963
      - Summer 1963
      - Autumn 1963
      - Winter 1963 (Box I:120)
      - Spring 1963
      - Summer 1964
      - Autumn 1964-1965
      - Winter 1964-1965
      - Spring 1964-1965
      - Summer 1964-1965
      - Autumn 1965
      - Winter 1965-1966
      - Spring 1966
      - Summer 1966
      - Autumn 1966 (Box I:121)
      - Winter 1966-1967
      - Spring 1967
      - Summer 1967
      - Miscellaneous
      - Special features, 1965
  - Controversy
    - Autumn 1963
    - Autumn 1966
    - Summer 1967
    - Spring 1970
  - Correspondence, articles for special autumn 1969 issue (Box I:122)
  - Copyright transfers, cross-reference sheets
    - 1951-1969, (16 folders)
    - 1969-1970 (Box I:123)
  - Corrections
  - Cybernetics, spring 1966
  - Delegate's manual, council meeting
  - Exchange subscriptions, correspondence, 1963-1973
  - Essay contest, autumn 1967
  - Financial survey, 1954-1956
  - Fuller, Buckminster, address at Vision 65 meeting (copies of letters sent and received) (Box I:124)
  - General
    - 1961, (2 folders)
    - 1962
      - A-M
      - N-Z (Box I:125)
    - 1963-1966, (8 folders)
    - 1966-1967
      - A-M
      - N-Z (Box I:126)
    - 1967-1970, (6 folders)
  - Haydn, Hiram
    - American Scholar
      - 1961-1963, (3 folders)
      - 1963-1970, (7 folders) (Box I:127)
    - Personal
      - 1960-1966, (6 folders)
      - 1966-1970, (4 folders) (Box I:128)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1960-1970, (11 folders)
    - Readers comments on "Humanism in 1984," winter 1965-1966
    - Replies to readers' reply letters, spring 1966
  - International solicitations, summer 1963
  - Journalism and mischief, Authors' Guild panel, 1968
  - Krutch, Joseph Wood, 1959-1970
  - Miscellaneous, bookstores, 1956-1968 (Box I:129)
  - Morality symposium, 1964-1966, (2 folders)
  - "The Old Left and the New," symposium, autumn 1967
  - Personnel, 1960-1969, (6 folders) (Box I:130)
  - Poetry
    - Contest
    - Submissions, 1969-1972
  - Portraits
  - Prairie Schooner
  - Printing and production, William Byrd Press
    - Bills
      - 1957-1965
      - 1965-1969 (Box I:131)
    - Correspondence
      - 1963-1969, (5 folders)
      - 1969-1970 (Box I:132)
    - General, 1960-1963, (4 folders)
  - Prints by New York, N.Y., painters, summer 1970
  - Privacy series
    - Promotion and publicity
      - Correspondence
      - Miscellany
  - "The Reader Replies"
    - Autumn 1960
    - Winter 1960-1961
    - Spring 1961
    - Summer 1961
    - Autumn 1961 (Box I:133)
    - Winter 1961-1962
    - Spring 1962
    - Summer 1962
    - Autumn 1962
    - Winter 1962-1963
    - Spring 1963
    - Summer 1963
    - Autumn 1963
    - Winter 1963-1964
    - Spring 1964
    - Summer 1964
    - Autumn 1964
    - Winter 1964-1965
    - Spring 1965
    - Summer 1965
    - Autumn 1965
    - Winter 1965-1966
    - Spring 1966
    - Summer 1966 (Box I:134)
    - Autumn 1966
    - Winter 1966-1967
    - Spring 1967
    - Summer 1967
    - Autumn 1967
    - Winter 1967-1968
    - Spring 1968
    - Summer 1968
    - Autumn 1968
    - Winter 1968-1969
    - Spring 1969
    - Summer 1969
    - Autumn 1969
    - Winter 1969-1970
    - Spring 1970
    - Summer 1970
  - Reprint permissions, 1960-1970, (9 folders) (Box I:135)
  - Reprinting, best articles and stories, 1956-1961, (2 folders)
  - Reviewers (Box I:136)
    - Autumn 1967
    - Winter 1967-1968
    - Spring 1968
    - Summer 1968
  - Royalties list
  - Southern Illinois conference (Vision 65) (Box I:137)
  - Unesco conference, 1960-1961
  - Undergraduate issue, autumn 1967
  - University Press book list, winter 1962-1963
  - Violence in Literature Symposium, summer 1968
  - Writers' Congress Symposium, summer 1966
  - Zahl, Paul, "A Look Around"
- Part I: Accession No. 17,500, General Editorial File, 1965-1972 (Box I:138-140)
  Arranged by subject and therein chronologically.
  - Board members, expired terms, 1970 (Box I:138)
  - Crime issue
    - Comments by prisoners, "The Revolving Bookstand," Aug. 1971
    - General, 1971
    - Correspondence, invitations and declinations, 1971
  - Controversy, spring 1971
  - Copyright transfers, cross-reference sheets, 1970-1972, (2 folders)
  - General correspondence, 1970-1972, (4 folders)
  - Haydn, Hiram, scholarship correspondence, 1972
  - Personnel, job applications, 1965-1972, (2 folders) (Box I:139)
  - Printing and production
    - William Byrd Press, 1970-1972, (2 folders)
    - Commercial publishers, 1970-1972, (2 folders)
    - University presses, 1970-1972, (2 folders)
  - Prisoners' contest, Aug. 1971
  - "The Reader Replies"
    - Autumn 1970
    - Winter 1970-1971
    - Spring 1971
    - Summer 1971
    - Autumn 1971
    - Winter 1971-1972
    - Spring 1972
    - Summer 1972
  - Reprint permissions, cross-reference sheets, 1970-1972, (2 folders)
  - "The Revolving Bookstand" (Box I:140)
    - Autumn 1970
    - Winter 1970-1971
    - Spring 1971
    - Autumn 1971
    - Winter 1971-1972
    - Spring 1972
    - Summer 1972
  - Summer reading, 1972
  - Tearsheets and reprints, requests for, 1970-1972, (2 folders)
- Part I: Accession No. 17,500, Author File, 1970-1973 (Box I:141-148)
  Arranged chronologically by fiscal year (Aug-July) and therein alphabetically by author. Author files for 1971-1972 are located in Part II.
  - 1970-1971 (Box I:141)
    - A-G, (7 folders)
    - H-Mc, (6 folders) (Box I:142)
    - M-R, (5 folders) (Box I:143)
    - S-Z, (6 folders) (Box I:144)
  - 1972-1973
    - A
    - B-F, (6 folders) (Box I:145)
    - G-Mc, (7 folders) (Box I:146)
    - M-R, (6 folders) (Box I:147)
    - S-Z, (6 folders) (Box I:148)
- Part I: Accession No. 18,559, General Editorial File, 1933-1980 (Box I:149-153)
  Arranged by subject and therein chronologically. Files for 1972-1973 are located in Part II.
  - Glass, Bentley, suggestions, 1965-1966 (Box I:149)
  - Black authors, names and addresses, 1969
  - Books
    - Winter 1975-1976
    - Spring 1976
    - Summer 1976
  - Comments on article by Pandarus (pseudonym), spring 1974
  - Cournos, John, review copies sent to, 1953-1966
  - Freeman, Robert Eliot, "Gov. Approaches to Social Problems," 1973
  - Harvard University Library, Cambridge, Mass., review, 1963
  - Haydn, Hiram, 1971, (2 folders)
  - Latin American issues
  - Love, Iris C., 1970-1971
  - Motherwell-Styron-Coles, tape on youth (Box I:150)
  - New columns, 1970
  - Odren, Richard, review copies sent to, 1960-1961
  - Original copy
    - Autumn 1979
    - Winter 1979-1980
    - Spring 1980
    - Summer 1980 (Box I:151)
  - Paperback book series, 1962-1963
  - Phi Beta Kappa (old files), 1933
  - Poet's issue, 1973-1974
  - "The Reader Replies"
    - Autumn 1973
    - Winter 1973-1974
    - Spring 1974
    - Summer 1974
    - Winter 1974-1975
    - Spring 1975
    - Summer 1975
    - Autumn 1975
    - Winter 1975-1976 (Box I:152)
    - Spring 1976
    - Summer 1976
  - Reprint permissions, 1964-1967
  - "The Revolving Bookstand"
    - Autumn 1973
    - Winter 1973-1974
    - Spring 1974
    - Summer 1974
    - Winter 1974-1975
    - Spring 1975
    - Summer 1975
    - Autumn 1975
  - Rockefeller Foundation, American Scholar features considered for publication in book form, 1957-1967 (Box I:153)
  - Scientists' project (old), 1973-1974
  - Standards issue, 1971
  - Tearsheets and reprints, requests for, 1973-1974
  - Women's issue
- Part I: Accession No. 18,559, Author File, 1973-1976 (Box I:153-165)
  - 1973-1974 (Box I:153)
    - A-C, (3 folders)
    - D-K, (8 folders) (Box I:154)
    - L-R, (8 folders) (Box I:155)
    - S-Z, (6 folders) (Box I:156)
  - 1974-1975 (Box I:157)
    - A-D, (4 folders)
    - E-K, (7 folders) (Box I:158)
  - 1974-1975 (Box I:159)
    - L-Q, (7 folders)
    - R-Z, (5 folders) (Box I:160)
  - 1975-1976 (Box I:161)
    - A-D, (4 folders)
    - E-J, (6 folders) (Box I:162)
    - K-O, (6 folders) (Box I:163)
    - P-S, (4 folders) (Box I:164)
    - T-Z, (5 folders) (Box I:165)
- Part II: General Editorial File, 1931-1988 (Box II-1-11)
  Correspondence, personnel data, and financial material relating to the operations of publishing the magazine.
  Arranged in chronological groupings and therein alphabetically by type of material.
  - 1930s (Box II:1)
    - General correspondence, 1931-1938
    - Miscellany, 1935-1937
    - Printing bids, 1931-1935
    - Promotion and circulation, 1931-1937
  - 1940s
    - Editorial board, 1943-1949
    - Financial papers, 1937-1949
    - General correspondence, 1941
    - Miscellany, 1942-1946
    - Promotion and circulation, 1946-1949
  - 1950s
    - Editorial board, 1953-1955
    - Financial papers, 1950-1956, (2 folders)
    - General correspondence, 1953-1958
    - Miscellany, 1950-1958, n.d.
    - Personnel
      - 1955
      - 1957-1958, (2 folders) (Box II:2)
  - 1960s, general correspondence, 1966-1969, (2 folders)
  - 1970-1971
    - Editorial board, 1970-1971, (2 folders)
    - General correspondence, 1970-1971, (3 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1970-1971
  - 1971-1972
    - General correspondence, 1972
    - Review copies requested, 1971-1972
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1971-1973
        - A-H
        - J-Z, (3 folders) (Box II:3)
      - Haydn, Hiram, 1972-1973
    - Editorial board, 1972-1973
    - Miscellany, 1972, n.d.
    - Personnel, 1972-1973
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1972
      - Winter, 1972
      - Summer, 1972-1973
    - Review copies requested, 1972-1973
    - "The Revolving Bookstand"
      - Autumn, 1971-1972
      - Winter, 1972
      - Spring, 1972-1973
      - Summer, 1973
    - Women's forum
      - Preliminary correspondence, 1972
      - Participants, 1972
      - Transcripts and notes, 1972 (Box II:4)
  - 1973-1974, general correspondence, 1974
  - 1975-1976, general correspondence, 1976
  - 1976-1977
    - Books
      - Autumn, 1974-1976
      - Winter, 1975-1977
      - Spring, 1976-1977
      - Summer, 1976-1977
    - General correspondence, 1976-1977
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1976
      - Winter, 1976-1977
      - Spring, 1976-1977
      - Summer, 1976-1977
  - 1977-1978
    - Books
      - Autumn, 1976-1977
      - Winter, 1976-1977
      - Spring, 1977-1978
      - Summer, 1977-1978 (Box II:5)
    - General correspondence, 1977-1978
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1977
      - Winter, 1976-1977
      - Spring, 1977
      - Summer, 1977-1978
  - 1978-1979
    - Books
      - Autumn, 1977-1979
      - Winter, 1977-1978
      - Summer, 1977-1979
    - General correspondence, 1978-1979
    - "The Reader Replies"
      - Autumn, 1977-1978
      - Winter, 1977-1978 (Box II:6)
      - Spring, 1978-1979
      - Summer, 1979
    - Who Reads Novels – A Symposium, 1978-1979
  - 1979-1980
    - Books
      - Autumn, 1978-1979
      - Winter, 1979
      - Spring, 1978-1980
      - Summer, 1979-1980